<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I’m Nazar Poladian</title>
    <link>https://npoladian.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I’m Nazar Poladian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:10:03 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://npoladian.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://npoladian.com/blog.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:49:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npoladian.com/blog.html</guid>
      <description>  Below are some links to my writing in various mediums. More to come… SOON!
  Artificial Intelligence 101
  Indindagous Communities in Canada
  SideWalk Labs and Toronto 
  DiverseCity Fellowship
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>https://npoladian.com/city-building-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:49:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npoladian.com/city-building-tech.html</guid>
      <description>Living in 5 different cities in the past 10 years, city building has always been my path to observe new cities and connect with various communities. That&amp;rsquo;s how I decided to take my passion into the next level by specializing in smart cities and urban data analytics at UCL, London to further explore how technology could bring various communities closer.
  Ping me a line if you want to further discuss smart cities strategy and startups, inclusive city building and public speaking or/and about below initiatives .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking</title>
      <link>https://npoladian.com/product-strategy-growth.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:33:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npoladian.com/product-strategy-growth.html</guid>
      <description>I have 5 years of cumulative experience in product/innovation strategy in various industries. From helping public sector leaders with their digital transformation programs, partnering with startups on formulating and branding their digital products and advising founders with their outreach strategy and growth.
  Ping me a line if you want to further discuss product growth, digital marketing, product innovation, digital transformation or/and about below projects.
  Projects   Deloitte: My last engagement was with a top Canadian bank helping them with project management, quality assurance and governance support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> من أنا</title>
      <link>https://npoladian.com/arabic/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:10:03 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npoladian.com/arabic/about.html</guid>
      <description>!حاليا أنهي دراستي في المدن الذكية والحضرية في جامعة كوليج، لندن
  كندا وأساعد المدن والوكالات الحكومية في تخطيط وإدارة برامج التحول المختلفة الخاصة بهم Deloitte أعمل كمستشار إداري
  (Royal Bank)عملت أيضًا في أكبر مؤسسة مالية في كندا
  حصلت على شهادة BBA في الإعلان والاتصالات ، وبدأت ثلاث شركات ناشئة في ثلاث دول
  شاركت بشكل كبير في بناء الجسور بين العديد من المجتمعات من خلال مبادرات اجتماعية مختلفة</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> من أنا</title>
      <link>https://npoladian.com/arabic/blog.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:10:03 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npoladian.com/arabic/blog.html</guid>
      <description>!حاليا أنهي دراستي في المدن الذكية والحضرية في جامعة كوليج، لندن
  كندا وأساعد المدن والوكالات الحكومية في تخطيط وإدارة برامج التحول المختلفة الخاصة بهم Deloitte أعمل كمستشار إداري
  (Royal Bank)عملت أيضًا في أكبر مؤسسة مالية في كندا
  حصلت على شهادة BBA في الإعلان والاتصالات ، وبدأت ثلاث شركات ناشئة في ثلاث دول
  شاركت بشكل كبير في بناء الجسور بين العديد من المجتمعات من خلال مبادرات اجتماعية مختلفة</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://npoladian.com/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 23:10:03 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npoladian.com/about.html</guid>
      <description>Whether it is a new operating model to implement, a business opportunity, or a political dilemma, I need to grasp it.
  Currently finishing my studies in smart cities and urban at UCL, London! I’m strategy and operations consultant at Deloitte Canada, helping cities and government agencies in their planning and managing their various transformation programs.
  Prior to Deloitte, I worked as a digital marketing consultant helping small businesses grow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>